{"quizName":["HTML5","HTML6","HTML7"],"quizSubject":"Programming","topics":{"0":{"topicName":"General","questions":{"0":{"questionText":"Which of the following tag insists to have a value in an input control in HTML5?","correctAnswer":"required","incorrectAnswers":["placeholder","needed","require"]},"1":{"questionText":"How to delete a local storage data in HTML5?","correctAnswer":"To clear a local storage setting you would need to call localStorage.remove('key'); where 'key' is the key of the value you want to remove. Additionally, if you want to clear all settings, you need to call localStorage.clear() method.","incorrectAnswers":["To clear a local storage setting you would need to call localStorage.remove('key'); where 'key' is the key of the value you want to remove.","If you want to clear all settings, you need to call localStorage.clear() method.","None of the answers are correct."]},"2":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the context menu for an element?","correctAnswer":"contextmenu","incorrectAnswers":["key","context","prop"]},"3":{"questionText":"Which of the following is correct about geolocation api in HTML5?","correctAnswer":"All answers are correct","incorrectAnswers":["HTML5 Geolocation API lets you share your location with your favorite web sites.","A Javascript can capture your latitude and longitude and can be sent to backend web server and do fancy location-aware things like finding local businesses or showing your location on a map.","Today most of the browsers and mobile devices support Geolocation API."]}}},"1":{"topicName":"Triggers","questions":{"0":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when media can start play, but might has to stop for buffering?","correctAnswer":"oncanplay","incorrectAnswers":["onbeforeplay","onplay","onplaythrough"]},"1":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when the message is triggered?","correctAnswer":"onmessage","incorrectAnswers":["onloadstart","onloadedmetadata","onloadeddata"]}}},"2":{"topicName":"Semantic tags","questions":{"0":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ should make sense on its own, and it should be possible to distribute it independently from the rest of the web site.","correctAnswer":"article","incorrectAnswers":["section","main","document"]},"1":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element represents a container for introductory content or a set of navigational links.","correctAnswer":"header","incorrectAnswers":["nav","aside","container"]},"2":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element the end of a document or section and often contains authorship information, copyright information, sitemap, and other elements.","correctAnswer":"footer","incorrectAnswers":["nav","aside","container"]},"3":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines a set of navigation links.","correctAnswer":"nav","incorrectAnswers":["aside","container","header"]},"4":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines some content in addition to the content in which it resides. Content within the _____ element should be indirectly related to the surrounding content.","correctAnswer":"aside","incorrectAnswers":["content","article","main"]},"5":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines self-contained content, like illustrations, diagrams, photos, code listings, etc.","correctAnswer":"figure","incorrectAnswers":["image","media","element"]},"6":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines the main content of the document","correctAnswer":"main","incorrectAnswers":["content","aside","article"]},"7":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ defines marked or highlighted content of a document","correctAnswer":"mark","incorrectAnswers":["emphasize","details","detail"]},"8":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines a visible heading for a different element.","correctAnswer":"summary","incorrectAnswers":["article","aside","details"]},"9":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines a date/time","correctAnswer":"time","incorrectAnswers":["datetime","timedate","timedata"]},"10":{"questionText":"Which of the following attribute specifies the semantic tag for the following:\r\n\r\n____ element defines additional detail that a user can view or hide","correctAnswer":"details","incorrectAnswers":["content","main","aside"]}}}}}
